(Penny:)but the other nine are on you.
(chuckles)
(Wil:)Thanks a lot, caller.
(Wil:)You know that the movie
actually has
(Sheldon:)a little bit
of a cult following.
(Leonard:)Really?
Yeah.
(Wil:)I was at
a science-fiction convention,
(Wil:)and I saw a woman dressed
as your half-ape character.
(Leonard:)Oh, if she was
(Leonard:)with an Indian guy dressed
like a banana,
(Leonard:)that was just my friends,
Howard and Raj.
(Wil:)All right, it's time
for a very special guest caller,
(Wil:)a friend of mine,
who you probably know
(Wil:)as the director
of such movies as Clerks,
(Wil:)or from podcasts and books
(Wil:)where he often reminds you
that he's the guy
who directed Clerks.
(Wil:)Hello, Kevin Smith.
KEVIN: Hey, man,
yo, is everything okay, Wil?
'Cause it's been,
like, two minutes
(Kevn:)and you haven't even brought up
Stand By Me.
Hey, Kevin!
(Penny:)It's really exciting
to talk to you.
(Leonard:)It really is.
(Kevin:)Oh, you guys are very sweet.
So, Penny, listen,
(Kevin:)I saw your movie.
(Penny:)Oh, wow. I wish it was better.
(Wil:)Oh, don't worry about it.
(Wil:)Have you seen some
of Kevin's films?
(Kevin:)You're cruisin'
for a beatin', Wheaton.